1~@~1~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate user by the login name, edit the contents, click the Save Button to make the change permanent or create a new user where permited. If user has SELF access to certain systems, please indicate all appropriate entities the user represents. Time-job scheduler requires "Anonymous" user to execute.~@~Unique login name and email address are expected for each user even though email is not mandatory. Do not hastily delete a user, it is best to append one or more "?" to login name and email then deactivate the user for further investigation. Information changed here do not reflect on "MyAccount" until re-login. Select Module:Administration if the picture does not show up properly.~@~User Manager~@~A new user has been created successfully.~@~The user has been updated to database successfully.~@~The user has been deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~2~@~2~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate table, edit the columns, click the Save Button to make the change permanent or create a new table where permited. Check Multi-Design-Database only for appropriate admin tables. Do not mention Permission Managed columns if not needed. No need to specify "ImportFileName" column. Make sure virtual is checked in the case of a view table or table function.~@~~@~Data Table and Columns~@~A logical table has been created; Synchronize to create this table physically if necessary.~@~This logical table has been updated successfully.~@~This logical table has been deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~4~@~5~@~1~@~Please add, edit or delete the appropriate user group and its authorities, click the Save Button to make all the changes permanent. The grid below will override the default authorities in the tab folder.  If there is a conflict within the overrides, the last one wins.~@~Note: Group #1 thru 9 are reserved, do not modify anything inside the tab folder; It is OK to override the default row & column authorities via the grid below. In case of conflict, specific shall override general in the order of (System, Company, Project), and the last one wins. Please note that this may not be deployed to production depending on the individual application's Configure Installer.~@~User Group~@~This User Group has been added successfully.~@~This User Group has been updated successfully.~@~This User Group has been deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~6~@~8~@~1~@~Please add, edit or delete the appropriate rintagi-controlled culture type, click the Save Button to make changes permanent.~@~~@~Culture Translation~@~Culture Type has been added successfully.~@~Culture Type has been updated successfully.~@~Culture Type has been deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~14~@~9~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate screen, edit the contents, click the Save Button to make the change permanent or create a new screen where permitted.~@~~@~Screen Definition~@~A new screen has been  created successfully.~@~The screen has been updated to database successfully.~@~This screen has been deleted successfully. Residual programs will be removed during regeneration.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~16~@~10~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate screen object, edit the properties or create new objects, click the Save Button to make the change permanent. Default sorting is on ref column of dropdown; Descending is assumed if sort column is the same as ref.~@~~@~Screen Object~@~Screen Object added successfully.~@~Screen Object updated successfully.~@~Screen Object deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~21~@~13~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate report object, edit the properties or create new object, click the Save Button to make the change permanent. Column Type "Parameter" is only relevant to SQL Reporting Service.~@~~@~Report Object~@~Report Object added successfully.~@~Report Object updated successfully.~@~Report Object deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~22~@~14~@~1~@~Please select a screen, edit the server rule, then click the Save Button to add or Save permanently. If content is available, the existing stored procedure in the database can be retrieved or replaced by the synchronization buttons.~@~~@~Server Rule~@~Server rule added successfully.~@~Server rule updated successfully.~@~Server rule deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~23~@~15~@~1~@~Please add, edit or delete the appropriate foreign keys, click the Save Button to make all the changes permanent.~@~~@~Foreign Key~@~Foreign keys have been added successfully.~@~Foreign keys have been updated successfully.~@~Foreign keys have been deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~24~@~16~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate screen object, edit the column authorization override or create new, click the Save Button to make the change permanent.  Entity type empty means default. The default before override is visible, editable and exportable.~@~~@~Object Authorization~@~~@~Object Authorization updated successfully.~@~~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~25~@~17~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate overriding row authority for screen or report or create new, edit the content and click the Save Button to make the change permanent.~@~Foot Note~@~Row Authorization~@~Row Authorization added Successfully.~@~Row Authorization Updated Successfully.~@~Row Authorization deleted Successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~30~@~22~@~1~@~Please add, edit or delete the appropriate default row authority, click the Save Button to make all the changes permanent. For Robot administrator, the robot-controlled Row Authority Default should be updated manually.~@~~@~Authority Default (ROW)~@~Authority Default (ROW) added successfully.~@~Authority Default (ROW) updated successfully.~@~Authority Default (ROW) deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~40~@~32~@~1~@~Please add, edit or delete the appropriate display type, click the Save Button to make all the changes permanent.~@~~@~Display Type Code~@~Display Types added successfully.~@~Display Types updated successfully.~@~Display Types deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~43~@~35~@~1~@~Please add, edit or delete the appropriate menu items, click the Save Button to make all the changes permanent.~@~~@~Menu Item~@~Menu items added successfully.~@~Menu items updated successfully.~@~Menu items deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~44~@~36~@~1~@~Please add/edit the menu items label per culture and click the Save Button to make the change permanent.~@~~@~Menu Label~@~~@~Menu Labels updated successfully.~@~~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~57~@~49~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate wizard, edit the columns characteristic or create new columns, click the Save Button to make the change permanent. Columns automatically filled when empty. No need to specify column "ImportFileName nvarchar(30) null" as it is automatically imported to the table but the table must have this column.~@~~@~Wizard Object~@~This wizard has been added Successfully.~@~This wizard has been updated Successfully.~@~This wizard has been deleted successfully. Residual programs will be removed during regeneration.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~58~@~50~@~1~@~Please select the wizard as criteria, edit the wizard rules characteristic or create new rules, click the Save Button to make the change permanent. @Overwrite char(1), @UsrId int, @ImportFileName nvarchar(30) are automatically parameters to each rule.~@~~@~Wizard Rule~@~Wizard Rule added successfully.~@~Wizard Rule updated successfully.~@~Wizard Rule deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~61~@~53~@~1~@~Please add, edit or delete the appropriate report template type, click the Save Button to make all the changes permanent.~@~~@~Report Template~@~Report Templates added successfully.~@~Report Templates updated successfully.~@~Report Templates deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~62~@~54~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate screen tab, edit the contents, click the Save Button to make the change permanent or add a new screen tab where permitted.~@~~@~Screen Tab Folders~@~Screen Tab Folder added successfully.~@~Screen Tab Folder updated successfully.~@~Screen Tab Folder deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~66~@~58~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate menu item, add, edit or delete the permissions, click the Save Button to make all the changes permanent. User and User Group applies to ALL while others apply to SELF only. All permission columns are independent of each other (OR) except Company and Project (AND). Denying one entity means all others are granted. Blank means permit ALL. Grant comes before Deny.~@~Multiple "Deny" does not work. Use "Grant" instead in that case. Please note that this may or may not be deployed to production depending on the individual application's Configure Installer.~@~Menu Permission~@~Menu Permission added successfully.~@~Menu Permission updated successfully.~@~Menu Permission deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~67~@~59~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate database, edit the contents, click the Save Button to make changes permanent or add a new screen filter where permitted. Main table may be represented as "b" followed by the TableId in filter clause.~@~~@~Screen Filters~@~Screen Filters added successfully.~@~Screen Filters updated successfully.~@~Screen Filters deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~72~@~64~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate user or other entity for this theme, edit the preferences, click the Save Button to make the change permanent or create a new theme where permitted. You may then grant or deny permission to any of the objects intended to show up on major sections of the page.~@~Please make sure there is a preference defaulted to each system or the menu for that system may not display properly.~@~User Preference~@~A new User Preference has been added.~@~Selected User Preference has been updated successfully.~@~Selected User Preference has been deleted.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~73~@~65~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate report, edit the criteria groups or create new criteria groups, click the Save Button to make the change permanent.~@~~@~Report Criteria Group~@~Report Group added successfully.~@~Report Group updated successfully.~@~Report Group deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~74~@~66~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate user by login name, edit the impersonation details, click the Save Button to make the change permanent.~@~~@~User Impersonation~@~User Impersonation added successfully.~@~User Impersonation updated successfully.~@~User Impersonation deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~75~@~67~@~1~@~Please select the report, edit contents, click Save Button to make changes permanent or create new report. Copy Report only function when report is empty. Template name is mandatory for rtf/txt document merging. Save Clause is for direct printing on template name with .txt only. Upon delete/name change, all obsolete programs/ s.procs will be removed except criteria still being referenced. Changing report types between Crystal and SQLRS may have severe consequence on the SQL controls, elements, and tables content.~@~Please note that Copy-Report works on new report only; Changing to SQL Reporting Service or Crystal Reporting for an existing report would result in all the contents in the Controls, Elements and Tables being replaced immediately.~@~Report Definition~@~This report has been added successfully.~@~This report has been updated successfully.~@~This report has been deleted successfully. Residual programs will be removed during regeneration.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~77~@~69~@~1~@~Please select the report criteria, edit the characteristic and help messages or create new criteria, click the Save Button to make changes permanent. Clauses are only useful when Display Mode is ListBox or DropDownList.~@~~@~Report Criteria~@~Report Criteria added successfully.~@~Report Criteria updated successfully.~@~Report Criteria deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~79~@~71~@~1~@~Enter your new password in the field below. Then confirm new password. Your password should be at lease 6 characters. Successful password change also reset the attempt count.~@~~@~Change Password~@~~@~Your password has been changed successfully.~@~~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~81~@~73~@~1~@~Please select the screen criteria, edit the characteristic and help messages or create new criteria, click the Save Button to make changes permanent. Select a criteria column from the relevant table for the data type.~@~Default sorting is on ref column of drop-down or auto-complete; Descending is assumed if sort column is the same as ref column.~@~Screen Criteria~@~Screen Criteria added successfully.~@~Screen Criteria updated successfully.~@~Screen Criteria deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~84~@~76~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate Screen, Report, or Wizard, add/edit buttons that should be different from default, click the Save Button to make the change permanent.~@~~@~Button Override~@~Button Characteristic Override added successfully.~@~Button Characteristic Override updated successfully.~@~Button Characteristic Override deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~86~@~78~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate password override type, assign the user groups, then click the Save Button to make the change permanent or add a new override where applicable. Prompt Modal does not apply to Screen Import.~@~~@~Password Override Type~@~Password Override added successfuly.~@~Password Override updated successfuly.~@~Password Override deleted successfuly.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~87~@~79~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate screen/report and culture, edit the client-side rules or create new rules, click the Save Button to make the change permanent. Only one of Screen Column, Screen Criteria or Report Criteria will be applied. Please only apply one script to each event;~@~~@~Client Rule~@~Client Rule added successfully.~@~Client Rule updated successfully.~@~Client Rule deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~88~@~80~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate Screen, edit the web rule, then click the Save Button to add or Save permanently.~@~~@~Web Rule~@~Web Rule added successfully.~@~Web Rule updated successfully.~@~Web Rule deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~89~@~81~@~1~@~Please add, edit or delete the appropriate button characteristic defaults, click the Save Button to make all changes permanent. Please make sure all buttons have a representation in English.~@~~@~Button Default~@~Button Characteristic Default has been added successfully.~@~Button Characteristic Default has been updated successfully.~@~Button Characteristic Default has been deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~90~@~82~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate version release to edit, then click the Save button to make all changes permanent; A new version release will be automatically created once dates have all been assigned.~@~~@~Version Tracking~@~~@~Version release has been updated successfully.~@~~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~91~@~83~@~1~@~Please select the release item to edit and press Save button to make changes permanent. You may add/delete accordingly. Not choosing db-Provider means universal for Data tier; Not choosing Framework means universal for Client/Rule tier. All [[?]] will be replaced by the appropriate namespace.~@~~@~Release Content~@~Release Content added successfully.~@~Release Content updated successfully.~@~Release Content deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~94~@~86~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate message, edit the content and press the Save button to make the change permanent.~@~~@~Message Center~@~This message has been added successfully.~@~This message has been updated successfully.~@~This message has been deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~181~@~87~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate database, edit the contents, click the Save Button to make the change permanent or create a new database where permitted. Be extra cautious with connection related info as accuraccy is crucial for logins.~@~~@~Systems Maintenance~@~Logical Application/Database added successfully. Physical databases still needs to be added.~@~Logical Application/Database updated successfully.~@~Logical Application/Database deleted successfully. Physical database and user preference unaffected.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~183~@~89~@~1~@~Please select the report style, edit contents, click Save Button to make changes permanent or create new style.  This is only applicable to SQL Reporting service.~@~~@~Report Style~@~Report Style added successfully.~@~Report Style updated successfully.~@~Report Style deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~184~@~90~@~1~@~Please select the report control, edit contents, click Save Button to make changes permanent or create new control.  This is only applicable to SQL Reporting service.~@~~@~Report Control~@~Report Control added successfully.~@~Report Control updated successfully.~@~Report Control deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~185~@~91~@~1~@~Please select the report element, edit contents, click Save Button to make changes permanent or create new element.  This is only applicable to SQL Reporting service.~@~~@~Report Element~@~Report Element added successfully.~@~Report Element updated successfully.~@~Report Element deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~186~@~92~@~1~@~Please select the report table, edit contents, click Save Button to make changes permanent or create new table.  This is only applicable to SQL Reporting service.~@~~@~Report Table~@~Report Table added successfully.~@~Report Table updated successfully.~@~Report Table deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~188~@~95~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate report, edit the content, then click the Save button to add or update. Only the owner of the selected report or system administrator has the right to modify. Grouping must be assigned to the first few columns in sequential order.~@~~@~Report Generator~@~Report Generator added successfully.~@~Report Generator updated successfully.~@~Report Generator deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~189~@~96~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate report wizard data category, edit the content, then click the Save Button to add or save permanently.~@~~@~Report Data Category~@~Report Data Category added successfully.~@~Report Data Category updated successfully.~@~Report Data Category deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~190~@~97~@~1~@~Please add, edit or delete the appropriate report data type, click the Save Button to make changes permanent.~@~~@~Report Data Type~@~Report Data Type has been added successfully.~@~Report Data Type has been updated successfully.~@~Report Data Type has been deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~191~@~98~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate deployment package, edit the detail, click the Update Button to make the change permanent or click the Insert Button to create a new deployment package. Target scripts should be always MsSQL based. All target design databases automatically get s.proc upgrades.~@~For each MsSQL data tier please have a corresponding Sybase entry for now, a dummy row is ok.~@~Installer Configuration~@~Installer configuration added successfully.~@~Installer configuration updated successfully.~@~Installer configuration deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~192~@~100~@~1~@~Please select the report chart, edit contents, click Save Button to make changes permanent or create new chart.  This is only applicable to SQL Reporting service.~@~~@~Report Chart~@~Report Chart added successfully.~@~Report Chart updated successfully.~@~Report Chart deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~195~@~103~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate Entity (used by Client Tier, Rule Tier and Data Tier) then click the Save Button to add or Update permanently.~@~~@~Entity Info~@~Entity added successfully.~@~Entity updated successfully.~@~Entity deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~196~@~105~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate Client Tier then click the Save Button to add or Update permanently.~@~~@~Client Tier~@~Client Tier added successfully.~@~Client Tier updated successfully.~@~Client Tier deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~197~@~106~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate Rule Tier then click the Save Button to add or Update permanently.~@~~@~Rule Tier~@~Rule Tier added successfully.~@~Rule Tier updated successfully.~@~Rule Tier deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~198~@~107~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate Data Tier then click the Save Button to add or Update permanently.~@~~@~Data Tier~@~Data Tier added successfully.~@~Data Tier updated successfully.~@~Data Tier deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~264~@~109~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate Maintenance Message, edit the message or create a new message, click the Save Button to make the change permanent.  Only one message can be displayed on the login page, the rest will be automatically set to 'N'.  Selected message can only be displayed when "DeployType" in Web.config is set to "PRD".  All active users can be informed upon the click of a button.~@~~@~Maintenance Message~@~Maintenance Message added successfully.~@~Maintenance Message updated successfully.~@~Maintenance Message deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~334~@~111~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate menu option, edit the advanced rule, then click the Save Button to add or Save permanently. In particular, the following CSS classes are available from the tree root "??Menu" where "??" is either "Tp" for top or "Vr" for vertical:

.??MenuSub represents the root ul list of each branch, including #??Menu;
.??MenuNode represents the li of the above which can contain one .??MenuItem and one other .??MenuSub;
.??MenuILink represents the anchor a within .??MenuItem which can have an icon .??MenuIcon and text;

.??MenuItem can also associate with:
a) .??MenuLevel_n where n=0 is the first level, n=1 second level, etc.;
b) .??MenuGrpTitle if this is a non-functioinal group title;
c) .??MenuItemSelected if the item is along the selected path;
d) .??MenuItemFocus is the last clicked item;
e) .??MenuItemFirst if this item is the very first item within a .??MenuSub;
e) .??MenuItemLast if this item is the very last item within a .??MenuSub;~@~~@~Menu Option~@~Menu Option added successfully.~@~Menu Option updated successfully.~@~Menu Option deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~652~@~112~@~1~@~Please select the Custom Label to edit and press Save button to make changes permanent. You may add/delete accordingly. Please exercise care while deleting Custom Label as it does not know which is being used by which program.~@~* Please delete label with care as it does not reference your custom programs. Changes made to "Administration" will be override by Rintagi upgrade, others will be override by application upgrade.~@~Custom Label~@~Custom Label added successfully.~@~Custom Label updated successfully.~@~Custom Label deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~653~@~113~@~1~@~This is where the business manager specifies the business rules that need to be implemented.~@~~@~Rules To Be Done~@~TBD Rules added successfully.~@~TBD Rules updated successfully.~@~TBD Rules deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~659~@~114~@~1~@~Please paste or enter the html codes and CSS as desired and press Save to make it permanent.~@~~@~Static Page~@~Static Page added successfully.~@~Static Page updated successfully.~@~Static Page deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~660~@~115~@~1~@~Please paste or enter the CSS as desired, give it a name and press Save to make it permanent so that you can share it with all your static pages.~@~~@~Static CSS~@~Static CSS added successfully.~@~Static CSS updated successfully.~@~Static CSS deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~661~@~116~@~1~@~Please paste or enter the Javascript as desired, give it a name and press Save to make it permanent so that you can share it with all your static pages.~@~~@~Static Javascript~@~Static Javascript added successfully.~@~Static Javascript updated successfully.~@~Static Javascript deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~662~@~117~@~1~@~Please upload the file or image as desired into dev/admstaticfi_?/ directory and press Save to make it permanent so that you can place a link to it on all your static pages.~@~~@~Static File/Image~@~Static File/Image added successfully.~@~Static File/Image updated successfully.~@~Static File/Image deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~671~@~118~@~1~@~Your specified url will be executed at the specific time or frequency you specified. Missed job will be executed immediately. IIS-refresh stops the timer. Timer will be activated as soon as someone sign in to this system. A summary email will be sent to the AdminEmail in the "Administration" DB. Requires "Anonymous" user to execute. All time expressed in UTC.~@~PageLoad in the program to be invoked should have something like: "if (IsCronInvoked() && ...) { UpdCronStatus(LcSysConnString, LcAppPw); }"; Currently highest frequency is every 2 minutes when no time is specified; Maximum wait time for IIS to check this job table is 15 minutes; All time expressed in UTC.~@~Timed-Job Schedule~@~Your schdeuled job has been added successfully.~@~Your schdeuled job has been updated successfully.~@~Your schdeuled job has been deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~673~@~119~@~1~@~Click the icon on the left to edit existing label. Refresh to see newly added.~@~~@~Label View~@~~@~~@~~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~677~@~121~@~1~@~Please drag menu items up/down to reorder and left/right to create submenus. When in doubt, handle the last item of the same level first. All changes are immediately updated.~@~~@~Menu IDE~@~~@~~@~~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~933~@~122~@~1~@~Please enter required information for SR&ED claims on selected members; Don't forget to associated newly created SR&ED member to their user login so they can enter their own time sheet.~@~~@~Member for SR&ED~@~Member for SR&ED added successfully.~@~Member for SR&ED updated successfully.~@~Member for SR&ED deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~934~@~123~@~1~@~Please enter time spent on the project using Rintagi to build applications. Describe with clear evidence of qualified work done on the project for SR&ED purpose.~@~~@~Time Tracking for SR&ED~@~~@~Time Tracking updated successfully.~@~~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~935~@~1001~@~1~@~Select a widget to add to the desired section or edit existing details. Please make sure background image is always the first one on the list for each section.~@~Please make sure background image is always the first one on the list for each section.~@~Section Object~@~Section object and details added successfully.~@~Section object and details updated successfully.~@~Section object and details deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~948~@~1003~@~1~@~This is the collective CSSs to apply to the column group and its div in the specified section.~@~Please enter or modify the CSSs to apply to the column group and its div in the specified section accordingly.~@~Section Column Style~@~Column Style added successfully.~@~Column Style updated successfully.~@~Column Style Deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~949~@~1004~@~1~@~This is the collective CSSs to apply to the row group in the specified section.~@~Please enter or modify the CSSs to apply to the row group in the specified section accordingly.~@~Section Row Style~@~Row Style added successfully.~@~Row Style updated successfully.~@~Row Style Deleted successfully.~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~971~@~1006~@~1~@~Please select the appropriate screen object and edit the multilingual label and messages, click the Save Button to make the change permanent.~@~~@~Screen Object Label~@~~@~Screen object label and messages updated successfully.~@~~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~972~@~1007~@~1~@~Please drag tab-folder/object up/down to reorder. Need to remove all objects from a tab-folder before deleting the latter. All changes are immediately updated.~@~~@~Object IDE~@~~@~~@~~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~984~@~1018~@~1~@~Sign up now to begin connecting and growing your business~@~~@~Sign Up~@~~@~~@~~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~985~@~1019~@~1~@~Please inspect historical changes using various criteria and filters, click the row to drill down for more details if necessary.~@~~@~Screen Audit Header~@~~@~~@~~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~986~@~1020~@~1~@~Feel free to inspect historical changes in details.~@~~@~Screen Audit Detail~@~~@~~@~~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~987~@~1021~@~1~@~This is a demonstration of paypal payment integration~@~~@~Paypal Payment~@~~@~~@~~@~View {10} more~@~Master list~@~Create or select a master record~@~Master record~@~Manage your master information~@~Detail list~@~Add or edit a detail record~@~Detail record~@~Enter or update detail information~@~No master record selected~@~No detail record selected~@~Click here to enter a new master record~@~Click here to enter a new detail record~@~Master records found~@~Detail records found~#~